Ajay,
hello friends, welcome to your
YouTube channel for HP. A few days ago,
we made a video on Reliance Capital
and there,
due to the process related to Reliance Capital, the name of almost 1
injured in acid was coming up as to
who can buy Reliance Capital. So, after
showing the complete information there, after seeing the complete intervention,
you also told that the
name of some other big companies can also come up in this, like we all
know that the first Reliance Capital,
which I had
said here, has to give the name of the coastal night masters
who
show interest in buying. After that, you must have seen
that the
time frame in it was extended a little, which
sir, the interruption was done till March
because
Reliance Capital should buy from many businessmen. Now they
want to buy the maximum amount of Reliance Capital because it is a very big
business market. If you see,
Reliance Capital is a very old company and has a huge
customer base. As they
know that whichever company has
more customer base, friends, its demand is
in the market.  There is a lot of customer interest in
this company, see, there
is a lot of customer interest here, the demand of those people who are tired of customer information is
very high, so
Reliance Capital is a very fulfilling company
and a lot of customers
use it even now, due to that
many people feel
that this is a profitable business,
Reliance Capital should be
invested in it properly and if
seen, it can give a good return in future, so
Reliance Capital will run, that means
if you run any company, you get
good benefits from the cross
or what benefit do you want on it and the
shareholders get it, so in Reliance Capital,
if you see the
names of all the businessmen who have come up for buying, friends, now we
can say that there is a great update
about it, so many people believe, they have been
saying for a long time that sir will
give a great deal, so see, this stock will give a boost,
then the question will come,
we will understand now that those who buy the
details of the airlines, there is a burden on them,  The
actual
insurance is given before buying any company, what is there in it,
like we have seen what happened in DHF,
what happened in Jet Airways,
everyone knows on the radio channel that whatever is its amount,
whatever is the recent amount till now, their amount was increased to
30, so we are that
whenever everyone sees such a share, that is, where there is a
purchase, regrettably, that someone is buying it with some force
and now this person is
buying it, then
you have to pay attention to what proposal has been made in it
and whose water is
getting the votes, so friends here
you will get to see a lot of things, you will get to see a lot of information about the
dance video regarding the shares of Reliance Capital
through this video, so the video is over,
then before starting, let me tell you that if
you want to open a trading demat account with Angel
Broking House or LIC, then we have
given it in the description of the video,
now you can definitely watch it, if you
need any information about opening a demat account, you
can also ask us by commenting, so
let's start.  Now talking about the stock,
here you can see that your
bill is given and we give you information about the stock,
after that through a lot of
information here through Brahmalok educational
experts, the mark within 6 months has
fallen by 32.81, like
in this, there was a son of Reliance Capital,
beyond this there is definitely a fault in it, so after that if you go
to Reliance Capital and whatever was invested in the late, the
price of that woman's model had
fallen a lot, so I show a
lot of decline in this T20 Bhikshusang stock,
and here you
see, inside the contract, the
return it has given is 30.90
650 of we fight, in this the share settled at 10.5 and
shown here and lost the ODI match, it
showed a rise once again, so you also
feel that if you see, then it is still
possible that you can see a rise from here
in this city, so friends, we have come here,
we
can see the NSS cadet on the website of Tennis, the dead
volume settings were seen from
2768 there.  1000 and fail over 10.00 vaccine
Ajay 30.62 back in an anti-clockwise direction, the
descendants of Zinc say that whenever you buy any shares, there
is great information about it,
try to take a
big position security wise, you can see the delivery
quantity Gautreaux on individual, it is
sixteenth leg, the
percentage of it is definitely around f-18 west,
so you can understand that there is a lot of buying happening in the city
or in the business sector, there is a
lot of demand in the market, the demand is because
some new company will do it once, which is
worship going on, which after some time, whoever
gets votes will buy it,
due to this, the demand for Reliance Capital is
seen increasing a lot, the stomach of
this medicine, the update that has come recently,
is a big update for Reliance Capital, for the
shareholders of Reliance Capital, here
you can see which companies'
names are coming, friends, but the name of the company
is Reliance Capital, so
what can be seen here  It was that Tata,
ABC, ICICI Lombard, and Nippon
Life, among the prominent Indian and foreign
financial companies that joined forces for the
profit-making insurance company Reliance
Capital, which was put under administration last year due to
deposits and
governance issues, came up here. If you
look at the name of Lombard Nippon Life, there are many big
names here, the names of big companies that
want to buy Reliance Capital.
Before this election, there was Mayawati's Adani Power,
which also came up. You can also see that the
name of the Japanese Adani Group also came up. There are
many such big investors
here. Right now, many are
showing interest in buying Reliance Capital. You
can see here that
the last day to submit expression of
interest to what extent by is
March 25th. To give access to the latest
information before the date of birth, make
financial bid to venture into the market, which you
mean many more or such interpress
Recently, companies whose lives will
access were shown for those who want to access, this was
extended, so these tips
which were building till March and see here
which big companies' names are coming up,
HDFC and HDFC Ergo Management
Financial Holdings Cholamandalam
Investments Adani Pinjar Yes Bank Poetry
Capital Blackstone Newcrest Industries
& International Book Field TPJ means a lot of
companies friends, if you see here then there are a
lot of big companies and among these the
very big ones which you will see are Caprio Bal,
after that there is Edelweiss, like the first one
is Motilal Oswal Financial Services
Square for Housing UP Malik's Yoga
Multiple, so many big
nurses, a lot of big companies should go now to
buy Reliance Capital, their
names are given in front, their names were shown
there, access was shown Alia date to
submit do you Ayush and interest
enemy which is of IS no entry, that is
Mans Liberty to avoid falling request
bikes Islam posted, so due to any such fear,
those people had to buy earlier but
which had gone to give  Master, they did
not cry about submitting the name, so they had requested
that its date be
extended towards the building. According to massage superhit, according
to the source, the
worst maturity of the readers have
submitted to you is best for the intercompany
half set for women and many subsidiaries
of Reliance Capital. So look here
friends, if you see such updates, it means
that if someone wants,
he can buy Reliance Capital, which is an anti-company company.
History in the building, Reliance
Capital, which means something different, can
also buy the fastest. Companies have to
see options. Enter the best for the day guide for
the enter Reliance Capital and any other all-in-one or more
of this quest for Reliance Capital.
Reliance General
Insurance, Reliance Life Insurance,
Reliance Securities, Reliance Asset
Reconstruction Company, Reliance Home -
Reliance Commercial Final Last November,
Reserve Bank of India had
brought a crush here, due to which the insurance against the dance was
brought in. So there are
many big businessmen here, many
breakups and its name is definitely worth watching.  It is being received
so that these people have given a proposal
that what will be the amount given to the existing shareholders
of Reliance Capital in retail, then
how much amount will be given to them,
then their shares will remain like this, so a very
big thing is pride, whoever has
shares in Reliance Capital, he has
bought them here, the other thing is that the
results are being seen from many big companies
and suppose India company like
Elastic Enter, who has bought it
and some big company has bought it, respected, then there is
someone else, so if you see, as we can see here,
big names like
KP Gupta, who bought it, they
told that whatever proposal has been given that the
shares of those retail investors will remain like this, only this is
their amount, that is, whoever has the
cap shoulder, whatever Shekhar,
in between, this question will keep going on, so
this will be a big
thing, if it comes here or any other
updates, then you must definitely see it
here, if you want to invest
in Reliance Capital right now, friends, then our
Request Saif, our question is about the
problem with awards, so here
you must pay attention once carefully that
right now in Reliance Capital, are you
without a bridge, after looking at its proposal, you will also see that there will be
different proposals from many companies,
note many many,
but the date till March for
submitting the name was, so there are many
such businesses like Suzlon company, the
name was submitted till then, send some nutritious things, that is why
you had not given the name in the building, the
request was made in the schools, that
withdrawal, the bring, the
date was extended till 28th March,
after that they submitted the name, so in English
friends, if you see in the list of many
big companies, its name is
Reliance Capital, to
do this, someone has to come and share,
friends, so right now the situation here is such that it has to be done,
if someone
wants to give, then he will do Bigg Boss, do
your research thoroughly once, so while
completing this video, the
purpose of the video song is that
Mukesh Mukesh will run in Reliance Capital  Let us share
that information with you through a small video. If you liked the
information given, then please
like and share it. If you like our
new YouTube channel, please subscribe
to Ajay
[Music]